<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Johandry&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.johandry.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Johandry&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 14:20:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.johandry.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Microservices in Go, part 1</title>
      <link>http://blog.johandry.com/post/intro-microservice-in-go-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 14:20:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.johandry.com/post/intro-microservice-in-go-1/</guid>
      <description>This is a very simple example about how to build a microservice in Go. It&amp;rsquo;s meant for a quick Go and Microservices tutorial series covering from the a RESTful API to gRPC on Kubernetes.
The purpose of this microservice is a catalog of movies. The code is at https://github.com/johandry/micro-media-service and every section is a branch, clone the repo and change branch for every section.
git clone https://github.com/johandry/micro-media-service  A simple RESTful API Let&amp;rsquo;s start with a simple RESTfull API by making a simple web server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Blog on Github</title>
      <link>http://blog.johandry.com/post/a-new-blog-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 23:42:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.johandry.com/post/a-new-blog-on-github/</guid>
      <description>Here is everything I did to create this blog with Hugo and publish it on GitHub. I don&amp;rsquo;t have to do it again but may help others to do the same.
You&amp;rsquo;ll need Hugo and Git. Once you have Hugo, create the blog with:
brew install hugo hugo new site blog cd blog git init  The next step is to choose a theme, which took me a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://blog.johandry.com/post/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 21:14:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.johandry.com/post/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Is it?
Nah! I think this is my 3rd attempt to start a blog. I started with johandry.blogspot.com then I started a cool project with PerlDancer and created this other blog perlondancer.blogspot.com. Also, there were a couple of failed attempts with WordPress.com.
I&amp;rsquo;ll continue posting, I have some ideas and projects that I have in my Github. Most of them related to Go and DevOps.
Stay tuned!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>